Hi, and this was an I want to show you all the power of after the complete in winter.
So we'll start from what is also complete. It's when you type something in surf top,
we'll offer some relevant code completions for you. I will try to predict what you want to write.
The case that you can apply all this out of complete. For example, when we just try to type something,
you will see this among gray out text. It's a suggestion. You have a few options to do with it.
You can accept it clicking on button right here or just click it up. You can also accept it
word by word. For example, if you don't like the whole implementation, you want to edit it or update
on a way and you can click, you can use the command + write arrow or if you own Linux or Windows,
you can use a control + write arrow. So let's try to do it. You see I accept it word by word.
And to accept it finally, like we can click just stop. And then again, okay, word by word,
so we can change something if you want, right here. And then just continue. Okay, but I'm going
to delete it. It's within needed. And what else? You can also move in a circle between all the
suggestions. Sometimes AI can do a few suggestions how you see implementation of a variable,
of a method or some other logic. And you can use these buttons to just move between them in a cycle
or just use a buttons. It is an option plus write square bracket and left square bracket,
depending on which direction you want to move. Or if you use Windows or Linux, you can use
instead of the option. But in our case, it suggests only one suggestion, so I can show you how it
works. Okay, the next nice option is top to jump. It's when we modify an existing code.
And a user feels a just modification. It doesn't matter with before the code we added in or
after. We will jump through all the file at top days is changed. I will show you.
Imagine we want to rename the password variable just to have a pass.
And you see when I finished, he shows us the next place where we can rename it.
I will just click outside and click pop. And then we have pop to jump with click pop again.
We first see the place and then we can apply it. Then we have pop to jump again and we have
more places to update it. And pop to jump again. I don't click my mouse. I just use my pop keyboard.
Okay, and I guess that's all. No, I can just click save. Okay, sometimes he don't see all the
places. So we need some. Sometimes I realize this place. Okay. What else? Next. Yeah, you see,
he just missed as this place. But when I just selected it, I just saw. Might be depend on the
model because we use, we use plot. So net. No, but it's for chat, not for this one before auto
completion is used. Something easier. So let me just search by password. And I will check if we
replaced all the variables. Yes, we do. But let's you see, sometimes it can be slow and not always
suggested. Okay. Um, the next feature is stop to import. I did one small change. I moved the common
patterns to the separate file and just exported it. And because I don't see any sense to keep all
this big array inside of the class. So I prefer to keep it separate. And inside of the class,
what I can do, I can just type common patterns and when short we'll see is that we have this common
patterns in another file and it does out the complete when we click on it. And scroll to the top,
you see the file will be imported. So this is a nice feature of auto complete. So now, you know,
how to accept completions, pull it over by word, you know, how to go through the cycle of the
suggestions, you know, how to modify existing code, we start to jump feature and how to easily import
some methods, which define it in different files, we start to import feature.
So also all this feature are customizable. If you click on the insert settings, you will see
you have insert top section and you have all the features. You can also hover on it and show
you. I'll detail it information and you can, for example, just of the auto complete on it,
you can choose the auto complete speed, you can choose also the super complete. If you want to
leave it, yeah, and you can do the same, we start to import the time to jump and you can, of course,
move it for 10 minutes. So if you don't need it right now. So it's up to you. Okay, I hope this
lesson was useful for you and see you in the next lesson.